# Awab Saif

Jiddah, Makkah, Saudi Arabia



Awabtaz9090@gmail.com



0550686506



linkedin.com/in/awab-saif

## **Summary**

Hello, I am Awab, a final year student in Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA) -Chandigarh University. Programmer and Frontend Developer, I have experience programming in html5, CSS and JavaScript I previously worked in managing the WordPress site and also in IT and data entry, At the university, I learned some programming languages, including C, Java and Python, I have experience in Office, Photoshop and accounting programs

## **Experience**



### website manager and IT employee

website manager and IT employee

Jan 2022 - Jun 2023 (1 year 6 months)

I am worked as a wholesale website manager and IT employee with Petra Stars Company

# \_ ma

### marketing of accounting software

marketing of accounting software

Sep 2021 - Present (1 year 10 months)

I worked as a sale and marketing of accounting software on commission and technical support for clients of the Kasab Information Technology Company

## Delivery

Mrsool app

Aug 2021 - Dec 2021 (5 months)

I worked as a delivery conductor with Mrsool app Simultaneously with the sale and marketing of accounting software on commission and technical support for clients of the Kasab Information Technology Company

## Distributor and merchandise delivery official

**Diamond Tawafuq Company** 

Aug 2020 - Nov 2020 (4 months)

I worked in an auto parts Diamond Tawafuq Company for 3 months

### Tickets employee

almosafer bus travel agency

Jan 2020 - Aug 2020 (8 months)

I worked for almosafer bus travel agency

## **Delivery Specialist**

## Mrsool app

Sep 2019 - Dec 2019 (4 months)

I worked as a delivery conductor with Mrsool app 4 month.

## marketing of accounting software

### Self-employed

Jun 2018 - Aug 2019 (1 year 3 months)

I worked sale and marketing of accounting software on commission and technical support for clients of for my father's accounting program

## Secretary

njd al majd company Jun 2018 - Sep 2018 (4 months)

## **Education**

## CHANDIGARH UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Computer Application - BCA, Computer and Information Sciences and Support Services

2021 - 2024

## Zamerica-n English app

English, English Language and Literature/Letters

Jun 2018 - Feb 2021

Pass the first level test

## Proleaders Institute

English, English Language

Dec 2020 - Jan 2021

Total training hours: 30 Grade: Excellent.

#### Khalid Bin Al Waleed Jeddah

High School , High School natural sciences May 2015 - May 2018

### **Skills**

Programming Languages • Microsoft PowerPoint • Microsoft Word • Microsoft Excel • Illustrator • WordPress • Adobe Photoshop • Marketing • Company Secretarial Work